Bob Bullock Campaigns papers, Inclusive: 1970-1996, Bulk: 1973-1996
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 1982 Campaign, 1974-1986; 3
  - Financial, 1979-1985; 4
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report (1 of 2), 1982 January 1-March 22 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report (2 of 2), 1982 January 1-March 22 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Contributor’s Lists (1 of 2), 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Contributor’s Lists (2 of 2), 1982-1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Invitations, 1981-1982; 5
    - “An Evening In Old San Antonio”, 1982 August 24 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - 414 Democrats, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Austin Democratic Forum, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Barrientos, Gonzalo, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Bentsen, Lloyd, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Bentsen, Lloyd, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Clements, William P. “Bill” Jr., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Democratic Majority Committee, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Dibrell, Joe, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Frost, Martin, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Hannah, John, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Harris, O. H. “Ike”, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Hobby, Bill, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Jones, Dr. Jesse, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Kilgarlin, Bill, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Kothmann, Glenn H., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Krueger, Bob, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Lea, Hugh O., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Lyons, E. A. “Squatty”, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Mauro, Garry, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Mauzy, Oscar H., 1981 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - McKnight, Peyton, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Moncrief, Mike, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Moya, Richard A., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Parker, Carl, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Pierce, George, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Richards, Ann, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Sherman, Max, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Snelson, Pete, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Texas Trial Lawyers Association, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Wallace, Ralph III, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - White, Mark, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - General: Declined, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Itineraries, 1982; 6
    - Fort Worth, Dallas & Temple, 1982 March (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Lufkin, 1982 March (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Wichita Falls & San Angelo, 1982 March (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Polls, 1979-1982; 7
    - AFL-CIO Public Opinion Survey, 1979 June 15-20 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Analysis of Bob Bullock Survey, Texas Research and Consulting Associates, AM, 1982 January 25 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Analysis of Bob Bullock Survey, Texas Research and Consulting Associates, PM, 1982 January 25 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Analysis of Bob Bullock Survey, Texas Research and Consulting Associates, AM, 1982 January 26 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Analysis of Bob Bullock Survey, Texas Research and Consulting Associates, AM, 1982 March 29 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Analysis of Bob Bullock Survey, Texas Research and Consulting Associates, PM, 1982 April 25 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Texas Research and Consulting Associates, 1982 March-September (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - The Texas Poll, 1982 February (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Position Papers, circa 1980; 8
    - Statement of Bob Bullock-Comptroller, circa 1980 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Publications, 1974-1982; 9
    - News Clippings, 1981 May (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - News Clippings, 1982 March (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - News Clippings: Editorial List, 1974 November 3-1980 February 11 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - News Clippings: Mike Richards Clips, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Press Releases: Supporting Peyton McKnight, 1981 June 2 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- 1986 Campaign, 1983-1987; 4
  For the fourth and final time in 1986, Bullock ran for Comptroller and won. The 1986 Campaign series has seven subseries: General, Correspondence, Elections, Endorsements and Questionnaires, Financial, Polls, and Publications.
  The General subseries contains general campaign information, and the Correspondence subseries includes correspondence from individuals, other politicians, and campaign staff members. Elections consists of general election candidate profiles. The Endorsements and Questionnaires subseries contains procedures, clippings of endorsements by newspapers, and questionnaires. Financial contains contributions to others, contribution and expense reports, and contribution requests. 1986 Campaign Polls includes information on election surveys and polling reports, and Publications holds news clippings and press releases surrounding Bullock’s political campaigns.
  - General, 1983-1987; 1
    - Announcement and Bio, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Slagle, Bob, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Slagle, Bob, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Richardson, Bob-Research, circa 1986 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Summary, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Summary of Fiscal Year, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987; 2
    - Mandell, Missy, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - White, Gov. Mark W., 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Staff: Castlebury, Glen, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Staff: Castlebury, Glen, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Staff: Proffitt, Tony, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Staff: Profitt, Tony, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Staff: Vilas, Leslie, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Elections, 1986; 3
    - General Election Candidate Profiles, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Endorsement and Questionnaires, 1986; 4
    - Procedures, circa 1986 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Newspapers, 1986 March (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Newspapers, 1986 April (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Newspapers, 1986 May (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Newspapers (1 of 2), 1986 October (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Newspapers (2 of 2), 1986 October (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Newspapers, 1986 November (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Dallas Morning News, 1986 April (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - The Echo, Humble, Texas, 1986 April (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Financial, 1984-1987; 5
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 January (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 February (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 March (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 April (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 May (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 June (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 July (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 August (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 September (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 October (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 November (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Contributions to Others, 1986 December (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Political Contributions List, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1984 January 1-June 30 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Campaign Contribution and Expense Report, 1984 July 1-December 31 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Contribution Request: Mattox, Jim, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Contribution Request: Nugent, James E. “Jim”, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Polls, 1983-1985; 6
    - Democratic Presidential Survey-Democratic Congressional Campaign Committee, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Education Poll Comparisons, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Judicial Poll (Mailed), 1984 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Texas Research and Consulting Associates, 1983 October (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Texas Statewide Survey-Shipley & Associates, 1985 November (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Publications, 1985; 7
    - News Clippings, 1985 October (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases, 1985 November (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases: Announcement to Run for Reelection in 1986, 1985 October 14 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 1990 Campaign, 1973-1991; 5
  The 1990 Campaign series is the largest and has twenty subseries, with several containing sub-subseries. This is reflective of Bullock’s massive campaign for Lieutenant Governor. The subseries include: Accomplishments, General, Border Master Plan, Gold Plated Agency, County Organization, Media/Advertising, Telephone, Correspondence, Transition, Elections, Endorsements, Financial, Invitations, Issues, Itineraries, Mosbacher, Polls, Position Papers, Publications, and Reports.
  After Accomplishments, the General subseries includes general campaigning information and materials used in political campaigns, such as brochures, bumper stickers, buttons and apparel, magnets, envelopes and letterhead, flyers, and faxes received and sent. The Border Master Plan subseries contains press releases, proposals, brochures, speeches, correspondence, and other materials related to the United States/Mexico border plan. Gold-Plated Agency, related to opposition research, contains correspondence, news clippings, press releases, and other items. The County Organization subseries holds correspondence, advertising, and Travis County specific materials. Media/Advertising contains correspondence, news clippings, and press kits, while the Telephone subseries includes telephone lists, action forms, and summaries related to the race for lieutenant governor.
  The Correspondence subseries has four organizational sub-subseries. The Transition subseries holds correspondence showing the materials Bullock had researched and put together to facilitate his transition from Comptroller to Lieutenant Governor. Elections consists of both primary and general election materials and analyses, correspondence, and reports on election results. The Endorsements subseries has six sub-subseries, the Financial subseries includes four sub-subseries, Invitations has two sub-subseries, and the Issues subseries has seven sub-subseries. The Itineraries subseries details Bullock’s travels for the 1990 campaign. It includes weekly and monthly calendars, schedules, and folders related to Jan Bullock. The Mosbacher subseries, pertaining to Bullock’s opposition, has thirteen sub-subseries. Polls contains information on election surveys, public attitude surveys, telephone surveys, polling reports, and analyses of polling information. Position papers detail Bullock’s position on critical issues such as budget, crime, drugs, health care, higher education, and jobs. The Publications subseries contains six sub-subseries, and the last subseries, Reports, includes the correspondence system report and weekly reports.
  - Accomplishments, 1988-1990; 1
    - Accomplishments, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Accomplishments, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Accomplishments, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - General, 1975-1991; 2
    - Bob Bullock Quotes, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Bob Bullock Victory Party Address List, 1990 November 6 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Brochure: Texas for Bob Bullock-Democratic Primary, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Bullock Appearances by County, 1987 September 10-1990 November 5 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Bullock filing for Office of Lieutenant Governor, 1989 December 3 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Bullock Legislative Record-55th Legislature-1957, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Bullock Memberships-List, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Bumper Stickers, circa 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Campaign Buttons, circa 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Campaign Memorabilia: Bandana: “A Special Texas Evening With Bob Bullock”, 1989 December 6 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Buttons: “On Target With Bob Bullock”, circa 1987 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Hat: “On Target With Bob Bullock”, circa 1987 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - T-shirt: “Bob Bullock For Lieutenant Governor”, circa 1990 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Candidate Profile Inquiry, 1989 December (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Comptroller Flight Lists, 1976, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Comptroller Revenue Processing Divisions Tour/Visitor Log, 1975 April-1990 August (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Staff Packet, circa 1989 August (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Envelopes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Magnet, circa 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Faxes-Received, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Faxes-Sent, 1990 January-March (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Faxes-Sent, 1990 April-May (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Faxes-Sent, 1990 July-September (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Faxes-Sent, 1990 October (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Flyer: “A Few Hundred Well-Chosen Words From State Comptroller Bob BullockEL”, 1989 January 25 (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - Flyer: “Bob Bullock, An Administrator for Changing Times”, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Flyer: “Bob Bullock-He Knows What He’s Doing, You Know Where He Stands”, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - Flyer: “The Right Man/ The Right Job/ The Right Time”, circa 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Flyer: “The Word Is Out”, circa 1987-1990 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - The Frankie Awards, 1989 October 20 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Inauguration Program, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Lieutenant Governor Letterhead, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - CPA Letterhead, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Border Master Plan, 1987-1991; 3
    - Building a “New Foundation” for the 90’s” Draft, 1990 August 7 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1990 June-August (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings, 1990 July (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Press Releases, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Proposal, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Regional Report-McAllen and the Border Region, 1990 July 11 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Testimony, 1989 September (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - “The Texas Perspective”, 1989 September (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Brochure: Bob Bullock-Democrat for Lieutenant Governor, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - People First, 1989 February (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - People First, 1989 March - August (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Report: “A Perspective on the Texas Economy”, 1990 August 23 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Skeet Shoot Button, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Slagle, Bob: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Slagle, Bob: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Speeches/Meetings List, 1987 September 10-1990 November 6 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Support Cards (blank), 1990 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Texas’ Lieutenant Governor-The Power to Make or Break Legislation, undated (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Wendler, Ed: Correspondence, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Wendler, Ed: Correspondence, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Wendler, Ed: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Wendler, Ed: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Wendler, Ed: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Gold Plated Agency, 1988-1990; 4
    - Correspondence, 1990 August (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1990 September (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - DHS Purchasing Orders, 1988-1990 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Itemized Lists, circa 1990 August-September (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - News Clippings, 1990 August-September (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Press Releases - Bullock, 1990 September (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Press Releases Mosbacher, 1990 September (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - County Organization, 1988-1990; 5
    - Correspondence, 1988 July (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence, 1988 August (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1988 September (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence, 1988 October (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, 1988 December (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1989 January (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, 1989 February (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, 1989 March (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 1989 April (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, 1989 May (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1989 June (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence, 1989 July (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence, 1989 August (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, 1989 September (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, 1989 October (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence, 1989 November (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 1990 January (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - County Advertising, 1990 August (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - County Advertising, 1990 September (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - County Advertising, 1990 October (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - County Advertising, 1990 November (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - County Advertising: County Ads-Original Artwork, 1990 October (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - County Advertising: Reel Tape, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - County Advertising: Siddons, Bill-Bullock Denial, 1990 October (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - County Coordinators Handbook, circa 1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Travis County: Bob Bullock Travis County Support Committee, circa 1990 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Travis County, 1989 August (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Travis County, 1989 September (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Travis County, 1989 December (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Travis County, 1990 January-April (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Travis County: Lists, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Travis County: Steering Committee List, 1990 June 6 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Travis County: Steering Committee List, 1990 July 1 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Travis County: Steering Committee-Top 100, circa 1990 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Travis County: Women Steering Committee Members, circa 1990 May (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Media/Advertising, 1988-1990; 6
    - Correspondence, 1988 January (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1989 April (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1989 May (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1989 August (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence, 1989 October (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence, 1989 November (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence, 1989 December (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 1990 March (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1990 May (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1990 June (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1990 July (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1990 August (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1990 September (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 1990 October 1-18 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1990 October 19-31 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1990 November (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Bullock T.V. “Buys”, 1990 September (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Bullock T.V. “Buys”, 1990 October (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Fundraiser Mailout Inserts, 1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Press Kit: Bob Bullock, Lieutenant Governor, ‘90, circa 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Press Kit: Bob Bullock, Lieutenant Governor, ’90-Master Press Kit, circa 1988-1990 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Press Kit: Bob Bullock, Lieutenant Governor, ’90-Master Press Kit, 1990 July (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Telephone, 1987; 7
    - Race For Lt. Governor-Secretaries List, 1987 September 10-14 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Race For Lt. Governor-Telephone Action Forms, 1987 September 10-16 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Race For Lt. Governor-Telephone Action Forms, 1987 September 17-22 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Race For Lt. Governor-Telephone Action Forms, 1987 September 23-30 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Race For Lt. Governor-Telephone Action Forms, 1987 October 1-7 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Race For Lt. Governor-Telephone Summary, 1987 September 10 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Race For Lt. Governor-Telephone Summary, 1987 September 11 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Race For Lt. Governor-Telephone Summary, 1987 September 14 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Race For Lt. Governor-Telephone Summary, 1987 September 11-October 14 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1987-1990; 8
    The Correspondence subseries has four sub-subseries, organized by: Alpha, Form Letters, Other, and Staff. It contains correspondence from individuals, other politicians, and campaign staff members.
    - Alpha, 1988-1990; 1
      - Adams, Don, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Bland, Craig, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Caldwell, J. Wiley, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Carr, Billie, circa 1990 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Harris, George G, Sr., 1988 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Yarborough, Ralph, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Form Letters, 1987-1990; 2
      - American Electronics Association, 1990 July (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Bullock Legislative Supporters, 1989 December 21 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - For Continued Support, 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Fundraising Letter, 1989 October (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Fundraising Letter, 1990 July (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Fundraising Letter, 1990 August (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Fundraising Letter, 1990 September (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Lobby Meeting Mailout, 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Mail House Information-Contracts, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Non-BB Contributors Letter, 1990 September (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Over $500.00 Letter, 1990 July (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - PAC Letter, 1990 February (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Pro-Choice Mailout, 1990 April (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Seeking Continued Support, 1990 November (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Senate Primary Race Letters, 1990 March-April (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Senator Luncheon, 1989 May 22 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Senators/Representatives Helping with Key Contacts, 1989 July 28 (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Lt. Governor’s Race-County Judges, 1987 September 24 (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Lt. Governor’s Race-State Agency Heads, 1987 September 23 (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Lt. Governor’s Race-Senators & Representatives (Texas), 1987 September 14 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Lt. Governor’s Race-TSAE, 1987 September 11 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Thank You Letters, 1990 June (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - To Other Candidate’s Contributors, 1990 April (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Under $500.00 Mailing, 1990 June (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Other, 1987; 3
      - Senator: Bentsen, Lloyd Jr., 1987 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Staff, 1989-1990; 4
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1989 November (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1989 December (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 January (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 February (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 March (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 April (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 May (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 June (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 July (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 August (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 September (Box 13, Folder 36)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 October (Box 13, Folder 37)
      - Outgoing-Claudia Stravato, 1990 November (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Transition, 1987-1990; 9
    - General, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - General, 1988 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - General, 1990 January-May (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - General, 1990 June 1 (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - General, 1990 June 26-29 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - General, 1990 August (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - General, 1990 September-October (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - General, 1990 November (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - General, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Elections, 1987-1990; 10
    - 1974-1986 County Results, circa 1987 November (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - 1974-1986 Graphics & Stats, circa 1987 November (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - 1974-1986 Summary, circa 1987 November (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - 1974-1986 Won & Lost Record Averages, circa 1987 November (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - First Primary Elections, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1989 November (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1990 January-February (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1990 March-April (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1990 November; circa 1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - “1986 General Election-At-A-Glance”, circa 1990 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - “Counties Lost By Bob Bullock”, circa 1990 November (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - 1990 Primary-Unofficial Results, 1990 March 13 (Box 14, Folder 15)